hi again it's Matt and now we're talking
嗨，再次是Matt，现在我们在谈论
a little more about strategic reasoning
有关战略推理的更多信息
and in particular let's go through and
特别是让我们经历一下
analyze the Canes beauty contest game
分析甘蔗选美比赛
now and talk a little bit about the Nash
现在，谈论一下纳什
equilibria of this game so remember what
这个游戏的平衡点，所以记住
the structure of this game was each
这个游戏的结构是每个
player named an integer between 1 and
玩家命名为1到1之间的整数
100 so you've got a population of
100，所以您有
players they're all naming integers the
玩家他们都在命名整数
person you'll name is the integer
您要命名的人是整数
closest to two-thirds of the average
最接近平均值的三分之二
integer named by people wins other
人们命名的整数胜过其他
people don't get anything ties are
人们没有任何联系
broken uniformly at random ok so again
均匀均匀地断裂好，所以再次
what other players going to do you have
你还有其他什么打算
to reason through that and then what
通过那来推理，然后呢
should I do in response so these are the
我应该怎么做，所以这些是
key ingredients of a Nash equilibrium
纳什均衡的关键要素
and the Nash equilibrium is everybody's
纳什均衡是每个人的
choosing their optimal response the one
选择他们的最佳反应之一
that's going to give them the maximum
那会给他们最大的
chance of winning in this game to what
在这场比赛中获胜的机会
the other players are doing that's going
其他玩家正在这样做
to be a Nash equilibrium ok so let's
成为纳什均衡好吧，让我们
take a look um so how would we can
看一下，那我们怎么能
reason about this suppose that I think
原因是我想
that the average play the averaged
平均打平均
integer named in this game is going to
在这个游戏中命名的整数将
be some number X so you know including
是一些X，所以你知道包括
my own integer I think this is going to
我自己的整数，我认为这将
be the average well what has to be true
是普通的井，这必须是真实的
about my reply to that my reply should
关于我的回复，我的回复应该
be 2/3 of X right I should be naming the
是X的2/3对，我应该命名为
integer closest to 2/3 of whatever I
最接近我的2/3的整数
believe the average is going to be so my
相信平均值会是这样，我的
optimal strategy should be naming an
最佳策略应命名为
integer closest to 2/3 of X so here
最接近X的2/3的整数，所以这里
we're just working through heuristic
我们只是通过启发式工作
aliy we'll get to formal definitions and
好的，我们将介绍正式定义，
analysis in a little bit but let's just
分析一点，但让我们
go through the basic reasoning now ok so
现在通过基本的推理就可以了
I should be trying to name 2/3 of what I
我应该尝试说出我的2/3
think the average is going to be well X
认为平均值会很好X
has to be less than 100 right there's no
必须小于100，没有
way that the average guest can be more
平均客人可以更多的方式
than 100 so the optimal strategy of any
超过100，因此是任何企业的最佳策略
player should be no more than 67 right
玩家应该不超过67对
so if I think that everybody's rational
所以如果我认为每个人的理性
I so if I believe that's true then I
我所以如果我相信那是真的，那我
think that nobody should be naming an
认为没有人应该命名
integer bigger than 67 ok so what what
大于67的整数好吗？
does that mean
这是否意味着
well that means that I can't think that
好吧，这意味着我不能认为
the average is any higher than 67 right
平均高于67对
so if the average ex is no bigger than
因此，如果平均ex不大于
67 then I should be naming no more than
67那我的名字应该不超过
two-thirds of 67 right now you can begin
现在可以开始使用67的三分之二
to see where this is going so that means
看这是怎么回事，这意味着
that if I think everybody else
如果我认为其他人
understands the game and understands
了解游戏并了解
that nobody should be naming a number
没有人应该给数字命名
bigger than 67 and nobody should be
大于67，没有人应该
naming numbers bigger than two-thirds of
命名数字大于三分之二
67 we keep going on this so nobody
67我们继续进行下去，所以没人
should be naming anything more than
除了命名之外
two-thirds of two-thirds of 67 now
现在67的三分之二的三分之二
obviously when you just keep looking
显然，当你继续寻找时
everybody's going to want to be a little
每个人都想变得有点
bit lower than everybody else's guests
比别人的客人低一点
so wherever the average is you should be
所以无论平均值在哪里
lower than that what's the only number
低于那个是唯一的数字
what everybody can be naming and
每个人都可以命名的
consistently choosing the best response
始终选择最佳响应
they have to what the average guess is
他们必须达到平均猜测
the unique Nash equilibrium of this game
该游戏独特的纳什均衡
is for every player to announce one okay
每个玩家都可以宣布
well that's yeah so so we're driven all
好吧，是的，所以我们被所有
the way down to a to announcing one and
一直到宣布一个
that's the unique Nash equilibrium and
那就是独特的纳什均衡
what happens now we all announce one we
现在发生了什么，我们都宣布一个我们
all tie and somebody wins at random if
所有领带，如果有人随机赢
if I try to deviate from that if I tried
如果我尝试偏离那个
to announce a higher integer I just be
宣布一个更高的整数，我只是
higher than the average guest so I
高于一般客人，所以我
wouldn't be at two-thirds of the mean so
不会是平均值的三分之二
this is going to be a stable point okay
这将是一个稳定点
so let's see what what actually happens
让我们看看实际发生了什么
when people play this so so part of this
当人们玩这个游戏时，
reasoning is you're trying to form
推理是你试图形成
expectations of what other players are
对其他玩家的期望
doing and you need to make sure that
这样做，您需要确保
those expectations actually match
这些期望实际上符合
reality so let's have a peek at some
现实，所以让我们来看看
plays of this game so these this is a
这个游戏的玩法，所以这是一个
plot here where we're actually giving
在这里绘制我们实际上在哪里
you the results of the online course so
您在线课程的结果，所以
when it was taught last year we had
去年教的时候
players play this game and so these are
玩家玩这个游戏，所以这些是
the results and here from 2012 we had
结果，从2012年开始
more than 10,000 people actually
实际上超过10,000人
participated in this particular game
参加了这个特殊的游戏
what do we see so down here on this we
我们对此有何看法？
have integers going from 0 to 100 and
具有从0到100的整数，并且
then over here we have the frequency so
然后在这里，我们有频率，所以
how many people name to give an integer
有多少人给一个整数命名
so the 50 right here is the the mode so
所以这里的50是模式
we get the mode of 50 the most often
我们最常得到50的模式
named integer was
原为整数
50 1600 people named 50 well obviously
50 1600人明显地命名为50口井
they haven't gone through all the
他们还没有经历过所有
reasoning and it takes a while to sort
推理，需要一段时间才能进行排序
of figure out what the the equilibrium
弄清楚什么是均衡
of this game is what's the mean here so
这个游戏的意思是这里的意思是
the mean was 34 so actually there's some
平均是34，所以实际上有一些
interesting things you some people
一些人有趣的事情
naming a hundred a number that could
命名一百个可以
never really win right so it's not clear
从来没有真正赢对，所以还不清楚
exactly what way it could end up winning
到底会以什么方式赢得胜利
if everybody named 100 then you could
如果每个人都命名为100，那么您可以
end up in a tie there but then you would
最终在那里打成平手，但是那你会
be better off
会更好
naming 67 instead so so when we we end
命名为67，所以当我们结束时
up looking through this what we end up
通过这个我们最终会发现
with is some people naming high numbers
与某些人命名高数字
but very few people then we end up with
但是最终只有很少的人
some interesting spikes a bunch of
一些有趣的峰值一堆
people just named 50 not clear exactly
刚命名为50的人不清楚
what the reasoning is on 50
50的理由是什么
interestingly if you think that a bunch
有趣的是，如果您认为那一堆
of people are going to do that you might
的人会这样做，你可能
want to name two thirds of 50 okay well
想要命名50的三分之二好
there's a big spike here at 33 where a
这里有一个33的大峰值，
bunch of people believe that other
一群人相信其他
people were going to name 50 if we keep
如果我们继续下去，人们会说出50
going so here if we keep going and
如果我们继续前进，那么就在这里
looking at this what do we see then we
看着这个，我们看到了什么，然后我们
see another spike at two-thirds of 33 so
在33的三分之二处看到另一个峰值
some people said okay well maybe a bunch
有人说好吧，也许一堆
of people are going to think that the
的人们会认为
average is going to be 50 they're going
他们将要平均50
to name 33 I'm going to go one better
列举33我会做得更好
than that I'm going to name something
比起我要说的东西
around 20 to 23 ah you know what the
大约20到23啊，你知道
winner in this game was the winner was
这场比赛的胜利者是
actually 23 so two-thirds of the average
实际上是平均水平的三分之二
guess here was about 23 the mean was was
猜这里大概是23
34 and so one of these people randomly
34，所以其中一个人是随机的
would end up being the winner of this
最终会成为这个的赢家
game okay um there's actually a spike of
游戏好吧，嗯，实际上有一个峰值
people who went all the way to the Nash
一路走到纳什的人
equilibrium and it's interesting here
平衡，这很有趣
because the Nash equilibrium works if
因为纳什均衡在
you really believe that everybody else
你真的相信其他人
is going to name the integer one then
将命名为整数然后
that's your best response but in
那是您最好的回应，但是
situations where a bunch of people don't
一群人没有的情况
necessarily understand the game and
一定了解游戏
haven't reasoned through it then you
还没有通过推理，那么你
actually would be better off naming a
实际上命名一个更好
higher number so Nash equilibrium is a
较高的数字，因此纳什均衡是
stable point if everybody figures it out
如果每个人都知道的话，这是一个稳定点
and everybody abides by it then it's the
每个人都遵守它，那就是
best thing you can do
你能做的最好的事
but it might be that some of the players
但是可能有些球员
aren't necessarily figuring out exactly
不一定要弄清楚
what goes on okay now suppose you start
怎么回事，现在假设您开始
with this game and they're not
这个游戏，他们不是
necessarily playing the Nash equilibrium
必然发挥纳什均衡
but now we haven't played it again right
但是现在我们没有再播放了
so they get to do this play it again and
这样他们就可以再玩一次
then see what happens well now these
然后看看现在发生了什么
people should realize that they over
人们应该意识到他们结束了
estimated right there's a bunch of
估计有很多
people here who are naming numbers too
也在这里命名数字的人
high they should be moving their
高，他们应该移动他们的
announcements to to lower numbers right
宣布降低数字的权利
they should be moving down and if if I
他们应该下降，如果我
anticipate that everybody is going to
预计每个人都会
adjust and move downwards I should move
调整并向下移动我应该移动
my announcement downwards as well so
我的公告也向下
let's have a peek at what happens so
让我们来看看发生了什么
here's is a subset of players actually
这实际上是一部分玩家
from from one of the classes I did on
从我上过的一门课上
campus where they got this is a second
他们得到的校园是第二个
play of the game so after the first play
玩游戏，所以在第一次玩后
then we haven't played again now you can
那我们就再也没有玩了
begin to see that things you know the
开始看到你知道的东西
50s have disappeared all the numbers up
50年代消失了所有数字
here have disappeared people have moved
这里消失了，人们感动
down and in fact a lot more people are
下来，实际上有更多的人
moving towards the equilibrium once you
一旦你走向平衡
get to the second part the second chance
进入第二部分第二次机会
so if you've played this game you begin
因此，如果您玩过这个游戏，就可以开始
to see the logic of it you play it again
看看它的逻辑，你再玩一次
and now we're getting closer to Nash
现在我们离纳什越来越近
equilibrium so Nash equilibrium does is
纳什均衡做的均衡是
a better predictor here if from
如果来自
experienced players who have played this
玩过这个的经验丰富的球员
game understood it and interacting with
游戏了解它并与之交互
the same population you can begin to see
您可以开始看到的相同人口
things unraveling and moving back
事情解散并向后移动
towards all announcing one okay so Nash
所有人都宣布可以，所以纳什
equilibrium basic ideas a consistent
均衡基本思路一致
list of actions so each player is
动作列表，以便每个玩家
maximizing his or her payoffs given the
给定最大的收益
actions of the other players should be
其他玩家的动作应该是
self-consistent and it's stable the nice
自洽的，稳定的
parts about this each player's action is
关于这个部分，每个玩家的动作是
maximizing what they can get given the
最大化他们可以得到的
other players nobody has an incentive to
其他玩家没有人激励
deviate from their action if an
如果他们偏离了他们的行动
equilibrium profile is is played someone
平衡配置文件被播放某人
does have an incentive to deviate from a
确实有动机偏离
profile of actions that do not form an
不构成行为的行为概况
equilibrium so these are the basic ideas
平衡，所以这些是基本思想
and we'll be looking at Nash equilibrium
我们将研究纳什均衡
in much more detail so in terms of
更详细地说，
making predictions you know why should
做预测，你知道为什么应该
we expect Nash equilibrium to be play
我们期望纳什均衡发挥作用
well I think there's sort of an
好吧，我认为
interesting logic here in this logic
有趣的逻辑
actually goes back to some of the
其实回到了一些
original discussion by Nash when we want
纳什（Nash）的原始讨论
to make a prediction of what's going on
预测正在发生的事情
in the game we want something which if
在游戏中，我们想要一些如果
players really understood things it
玩家真的很懂事
would be consistent and the interesting
将是一致的和有趣的
thing is we should expect non equilibria
事情是我们应该期待非平衡
not to be stable in the sense that if
不稳定，如果
players understood it and see what
玩家了解它，然后看什么
happens in a non equilibrium they should
发生在非平衡状态，他们应该
move away from that and we saw exactly
远离那个，我们看到了
that in the second round of the beauty
在美丽的第二轮
contest game then people start moving
比赛游戏，然后人们开始移动
down towards the Nash equilibrium so
向下走向纳什均衡，所以
it's not necessarily true that we always
我们总是不一定
expect equilibrium to be played but we
期望发挥平衡，但是我们
should expect non equilibria to vanish
应该期待不平衡消失
over time and there'll be various
随着时间的流逝，将会有各种各样的
dynamics and other kinds of settings
动态和其他种类的设置
where there will be strong pushes
哪里会有强大的推动力
towards equilibrium over time but they
随着时间的流逝达到平衡，但他们
might have to be learned and they might
可能需要学习，他们可能
have to evolve and and so forth so as
必须发展等等
course goes on we'll talk more and more
当然，我们会越来越多地谈论
about some of the dynamics and things
关于一些动态和事物
that push towards Nash equilibrium
推动纳什均衡